http://www.summerfun.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy | Summer Discovery
Register: After School Clubs Webinar Summer DiscoveryCampusesHigh School Pre-CollegeUCLAUCLA Anderson BusinessUC Santa BarbaraUCSB & UCLAU Colorado BoulderU Texas AustinU MichiganU Michigan & UCLAGeorgetown UJohns HopkinsPennPenn LawWhartonCambridge ULondonCambridge U & LondonYale-NUS SingaporeSD OnlineMiddle SchoolUCLA Middle School EnrichmentGeorgetown Middle School EnrichmentAcademics Arts & Design
Business & Entrepreneurship
Law & Government
Leadership
Life Skills
Medicine
Social Sciences
Sports Management & E-Sports
STEM
Middle School Enrichment ResourcesCOVID-19 UpdatesDates & TuitionHow To ApplySafety & SecurityFAQInternational StudentsEnrollment Terms & ConditionsPayment & Cancellation PolicyTuition / Travel Protection PlanWebinarBlogGet InfoApply NowWhy Us?BenefitsCustomer CareLeadershipOur StudentsScholarshipsCampus & Location Finder
Privacy Policy Here at summerdiscovery.com, we are sensitive to protecting the private information that you provide to us. Our mission is to offer you useful information about enrichment and travel programs that are owned and operated by Musiker Discovery Programs, Inc. We want you to have the opportunity to receive information about Summer Discovery and Jr. Discovery, as well as enjoy other online capabilities, such as online enrollment and catalog request that summerdiscovery.com provides. In order for summerdiscovery.com to make those services available, we ask you to submit personal information. This policy will give details on how summerdiscovery.com uses the information that you provide to us and why we ask for the information that we do. We may make changes to this policy periodically, which we will post here.Personal InformationWhile visiting summerdiscovery.com, there may be times that we will ask you to submit personal information in order to provide better service and/or additional information to you.SUMMERDISCOVERY.COM will not sell or rent any personal information to any other companies or organizations.SUMMERDISCOVERY.COM will only collect personal information that is necessary to conduct our business.SUMMERDISCOVERY.COM does not share your billing information with any other companies or organizations except to process your credit card for your Summer Discovery and/or Jr. Discovery payment, or unless required by law.Personal information is information that you provide that identifies you. You will be asked to disclose personal information on summerdiscovery.com when you (a) request a catalog, (b) apply for Summer Discovery & Jr. Discovery online, (c) apply for a summer job online, and/or (d) email summerdiscovery.com.Summer Discovery DisclaimerOur goal at summerdiscovery.com is to provide you with an informative, fun, and user-friendly website. In doing so, we have posted content and material that we feel is suitable to our users. We have also provided links to other web sites that you will find appropriate and informative. However, summerdiscovery.com does not endorse the accuracy or reliability of any information or content contained on or the distribution through websites linked to or from this website. Users that view sites linked off summerdiscovery.com do so of their accord and reliance upon any information or material shall be at the users sole risk. Additionally, summerdiscovery.com is not responsible for the copyright compliance, legality, or decency of material contained in sites linked to from this website or subsequent links from other sites.If you have any questions or comments in regard to the summerdiscovery.com privacy policy or disclaimer please email info@summerdiscovery.com
top
Blog
About
Contact
Partnerships
International Agents
Summer Jobs
Site Search
Payment & Cancellation Policy
Enrollment Terms & Conditions
Privacy Policy
Terms of Use
Alumni
Site Map FacebookTwitterYouTubePinterestInstagramGet InfoApply NowPhone516-621-3939 - General 516-625-3438 - FaxOffice HoursMon. - Thurs. 9:30 AM - 6:00 PM EST Fri. 9:30 AM - 5:00 PM EST Sat. hours vary1326 Old Northern Blvd Roslyn, NY 11576info@summerdiscovery.com© 2020 Musiker Discovery Programs, Inc. All rights reserved.Site by Baby Steps
